inticketing.com 2009-04-10

# Your privacy

We are committed to protecting your privacy. When you place an order with us, your personal information and credit card information are safe. Please read on for more details about our privacy policy. 

**What information do we collect?**  
When you order, we need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card number, and expiration date. This allows us to process your order and notify you of your order status. Only the expiration date and the last five digits of your credit card will be stored in our database. This is done to ensure that no one will be able to access your credit card information once your transaction is complete. 

We use your Internet Protocol (IP) address to help diagnose problems with our computer server and to administer our web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and gather broad demographic data. Your IP address contains no personal information about you. Our site may contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. 

**How is customer information protected?**  
When you place orders or access your account information, we make use of a secure server using 128 bit encryption. 128 bit encryption is the highest level of security available on the Internet. In addition we have an authorized Secure Server certificate from a third party verification service. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. In addition, all of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access. 

**Will my information be sold?**  
NO! We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. We may provide aggregate statistics about our site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information. 

**Your questions and comments**  
Feel free to contact us any time and we'll answer any additional questions. A real person will get back to you.
